bookmarkbay.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Bookmarkbay

**Your acceptance of these Privacy Policy terms**

By using any of the sites within our web site network ("Bookmarkbay.com") or   
our Services, you unconditionally agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.  
  
**What data do we collect and how do we use it?**

**_Bookmarkbay.com_** collects and processes information about you in order to:

(1) identify you each time you visit a Web Site or wish to have a Service provided;   
(2) process orders or applications submitted by you;   
(3) improve our Services and Web Sites   
(4) Customise your experience, for example, provide advertisements that we think   
are relevant to you and which support any specific requests for information you  
may make through keyword searches;   
(5) carry out research on the demographics, interests and behaviour of all of our   
customers;   
(6) send you information we think you may find useful, including information about   
new **_Bookmarkbay.com_** products and services.

You may be asked, either when you register with us, or at other times, for information  
about yourself, such as your name, e-mail address, postal address and telephone   
number. You may also be asked to share with us your interests, hobbies and preferences.  
In addition, when you order certain goods or services from our Web Sites, we will  
need to know your credit/payment card number and expiration date.

You are under no obligation to provide this information, but if you don't then we may   
not be able to provide you with certain services or personalise your experience and  
tailor our Services for you (for example, tell you about special offers on things  
you're interested in). 

**Log files/IP addresses**

When you visit our Web Sites, we automatically log your IP address (the unique   
address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically  
recognised by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer our Web  
Sites and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not  
link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.

**Non personal information**

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type  
of internet browsers you use or the site from which you linked to our Web Sites. You   
cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an   
effective service on our Web Sites. We may from time to time supply the owners or   
operators of third party sites from which it is possible to link to our Web Sites with   
information relating to the number of users linking to our Web Sites from their sites.  
You cannot be identified from this information.

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web Site transfers to your hard drive to store   
and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept  
cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. However,  
you may not be able to take full advantage of a Web Site if you do so. Cookies are  
specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers,   
which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Although  
they do identify a user's computer, cookies do not personally identify customers  
or passwords. Credit card information is not stored in cookies.

**We use cookies for the following reasons:  
** (1) To identify who you are and to access your account information;   
(2) To estimate our audience size and patterns;   
(3) To ensure that you are not asked to register twice;   
(4) To control how often visitors see similar ads;   
(5) To track preferences and to improve and update our Web Site; and   
(6) To track the progress and number of entries in some of our promotions and contests.   
**With whom is the information shared?**

**_Bookmarkbay.com_** will not share, sell or rent your personal information to  
third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information to third party   
suppliers who provide services on our behalf.

**** **_Bookmarkbay.com_** may disclose aggregate statistics about our sales, our   
Web Site visitors and customers of our telephone services in order to describe our   
services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for   
other lawful purposes, but these statistics will not include personally identifying   
information.

******_Bookmarkbay.com _** may disclose personal information if required to do so  
by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights,  
property or personal safety of company name and its Web Sites, visitors to the   
Web Sites and customers of our Services.

Our Web Site contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites,  
we suggest that you read their privacy policies. **_Bookmarkbay.com_** **** is not  
responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites. 

We will only sell or rent your personal information to a third party either as part of a  
sale of the assets of a **__** **_Bookmarkbay.com_** website or having ensured that   
steps have been taken to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

**Information about products and services**

It is very important to us that we provide you with the highest level of service. In   
order to help us do this, from time to time **_Bookmarkbay.com_** website  
may send you details of our products and services which we think may be of interest  
to you. If at any time you do not wish to receive these details, please e-mail us  
at [info@athifea.com](mailto:info@athifea.com)

**Security**

******_Bookmarkbay.com_** places a great importance on the security of all information  
associated with our customers. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect   
against the loss, misuseand alteration of customer data under our control. For example, our   
security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only  
authorised personnel have access to user information. With regard to our Web Sites, we use  
secure server software (SSL) to encrypt financial information you input before it is sent to us.  
While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur,   
we use our best efforts to prevent this.

**Where is the information stored?**

Information which you submit via our Web Sites or our telephone services is stored  
on a computer located in the USA Area. This is necessary in order to process the   
information and to send you any information you have requested. Information   
submitted by you may be transferred by us to our other offices and to reputable third  
party suppliers, which may be situated outside the USA Area. Not all countries   
outside the USA have data protection or privacy laws. In addition, if you use our  
Services while you are outside the USA, your information may be transferred   
outside the USA in order to provide you with those Services.  
****

**Comments**

Please e-mail any questions, concerns or comments you have about our Privacy   
Policy to [info@athifea.com](mailto:info@athifea.com) **_  
_**
